This is number four of my five favorite
buy for life items. This is the Olympus
XA2 film camera. This is a analog film
camera that was actually made in the
'80s. Personally, I'm kind of sick of
buying new cameras where sometimes they
literally require an app [music] for you
to even start using it, and then the app
gets all buggy, then the camera stops
working. So, it's really refreshing
sometimes to just use [music] a film
camera that has none of that. It doesn't
even require me to bring my phone out.
If you think about it, this camera has
[music]
been functional for over 45 years, maybe
50 years. The fact that 50 years later,
this camera still works, there really no
issues with it, and it still takes
[music] amazing photos, goes to show how
amazing the build quality is back in
those times.